Luis Olmos

367 Dos Amigos Dr. Del Rio, TX 78840 (830) 734-5019 olmos.luisd@outlook.com

Summary

I am a working graphic designer, with a few extra skills in photography, videography, and website coding. Being creative allows me to explore different ways of expressing myself and discovering more about myself as a graphic designer. I wouldn't be in this line of work if I didn't enjoy what I love doing.

Skills

- Graphic Design 1 year
- Photography
- Videography
- Adobe Creative Cloud (2 Years):
 - Illustrator
 - Photoshop
 - InDesign
 - After Effects
 - Premiere
 - XD
 - Dreamweaver
- Full Stack Coding:
 - o HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
 - JQuery
 - Bootstrap
 - o Express.js and Node.js
 - MySQL and NoSQL
 - MongoDB and Mongoose

Experience

October 2021 - April 2022

Stripes- Harlingen, Texas - Sales Associate

- Customer Service and Cashier services
- Cleaning and organization

November 2022 - Current

Ventura Promotional Products- Del Rio, Texas - Graphic Designer

- Designing and organizing our company's catalog
- Putting together email blasts to be sent off to clients
- Taking photos of new products
- Photo editing
- Adding new products to the website

Education

September 2020 - April 2022

Texas State Technical College in Harlingen - Associate's of Applied Science in Digital Media Design

GPA: 3.667

August 2023 - February 2024

University of Texas at San Antonio Coding Bootcamp - Certificate of Completion

Expected: February 16, 2024